<errors>
  <error type="CUSTOM" code="500">
    <message lang="en">%s</message>
  </error>
  <error type="LOGOUT-FOR-MAINTENANCE" code="503">
    <message lang="en">You have been automatically logged out from the application to allow us to perform some maintenance operations. We apologize for any inconvenience. Please come back later.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="BROWSER-WARNING" code="500">
    <message lang="en">The Coach Match application is actually compatible with the Firefox web browser. It has been reported to work on Chrome and Safari too. We have plan to support recent versions of Internet Explorer but this is not available yet. Since your web browser seems to be Internet Explorer (user agent : "%s") please switch to another supported web brower in the meantime. We apologize for the inconvenience.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="HOLD" code="401">
    <message lang="fr">Maintenance de l'application, merci de revenir dans quelques minutes...</message>
    <message lang="en">Maintenance in progress, please come back in a few minutes...</message>
  </error>
  <error type="FORBIDDEN" code="401">
    <message lang="fr">Vous n'avez pas les autorisations nécessaires pour effectuer cette opération</message>
    <message lang="de">Sie sind nicht befugt diese Aktion durchzuführen</message>
    <message lang="en">You don't have the access rights to perform this action</message>
  </error>
  <error type="NOT-IMPLEMENTED-YET" code="500">
    <message lang="fr">Cette fonctionnalité sera bientôt disponible</message>
    <message lang="de">Diese Funktion wird bald verfügbar sein</message>
    <message lang="en">This function is not available yet</message>
  </error>
  <error type="INCOMPLETE-APP-CONFIG" code="500">
    <message lang="en">Incomplete application configuration, please contact an administrator</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CV-FILE-NOT-FOUND" code="404">
    <message lang="en">CV file not found in person's profile</message>
  </error>
  <error type="APPLICATION-ALREADY-SUBMITTED" code="401">
    <message lang="en">You cannot submit your application once again as the first one has not been processed</message>
  </error>
  <error type="APPLICATION-MISSING-DATA" code="404">
    <message lang="en">You need to complete your profile first. You must at least either upload your CV as a PDF file or enter a link to your CV in the section about your Experiences. You must also edit your Executive summary in the section about your Competences.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="APPLICATION-KEEP-EITHER-CV" code="404">
    <message lang="en">You are registered as an applicant for %s host so it is mandatory that you keep at least either your CV as a PDF file or a link to your CV in the Experiences section.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="MODE-WARNING-TEST">
    <message lang="en">This is a TEST SERVER only ! If your intent is to use the real Coach Match application, then check the URL you are using. Information on this platform may not be accurate and can be lost at any time...</message>
  </error>
  <error type="MODE-WARNING-DEV">
    <message lang="en">This is a DEVELOPMENT SERVER only ! If your intent is to use the real Coach Match application, then check the URL you are using. Information on this platform may not be accurate and can be lost at any time...</message>
  </error>
  <!-- ************************************* -->
  <!-- ************ CAS Errors ************* -->
  <!-- ************************************* -->
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-GET">
    <message lang="en">The URL specified for contacting %s (%s) is invalid as a mandatory parameter is lacking.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-INIT">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s while initializing login: %s.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-INIT-NO-RULES">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s while initializing login. No way has been provided to process for HTTP code %s.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-INIT-NO-VALID-RULES">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s while initializing login. No way available to process for HTTP code %s can be applied to the context of the response.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-INIT-MISMATCHING-RULES">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s while initializing login. Failures and successes have to be enforced at the same time for processing the result of the HTTP code %s.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-NOTHING-TO-RETURN">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s. Succeeded init. has returned nothing (%s).</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-INVALID-VAL">
    <message lang="en">An error has been raised by %s while validating the ticket: %s.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ECAS-NO-USER-PROFILE">
    <message lang="en">You must register a user account using the link on the login page before browsing the site</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CAS-LOGIN-FAILED">
    <message lang="en">Authentication with %s is misconfigured in Coach Match application, please tell an administrator</message>
  </error>
  <error type="REMOTE-PROFILE-MISSING-DATA" code="409">
    <message lang="en">Both the external login and the related realm are needed</message>
  </error>
  <!-- **************************************************** -->
  <!-- ************ Generic Validation Errors ************* -->
  <!-- **************************************************** -->
  <error type="BAD-REQUEST" code="409">
    <message lang="en">Bad request, unrocognized data</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-FORMAT-ERROR" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Les données soumises au serveur ne sont pas dans le bon format, merci de signaler cette erreur à un administrateur</message>
    <message lang="de">Die beim Server eingetragenen Daten haben nicht das richtige Format, bitte melden Sie diesen Fehler beim Systemmanager</message>
    <message lang="en">The data submitted to the server does not have the correct format. Please report this error to an administrator</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-ROOT-ERROR" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Le document soumis au serveur n'appartient pas au bon vocabulaire (reçu : %s), merci de signaler cette erreur à un administrateur</message>
    <message lang="de">Das beim Server gemeldete Dokument ist fehlerhaften Ursprungs (empfangen : %s), bitte melden Sie diesen Fehler beim Systemmanager</message>
    <message lang="en">The document submitted to the server does not have the correct root (received : %s). Please report this error to a database administrator</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-FAILED" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Données invalides, corrigez la saisie (%s)</message>
    <message lang="de">Daten ungültig, bitte erneut eingeben. (%s)</message>
    <message lang="en">Invalid data, please correct the entry (%s)</message>
  </error>
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <!-- ************ User Management ************* -->
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <error type="DELETE-PERSON-FORBIDDEN" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Vous ne pouvez pas supprimer %s. %s</message>
    <message lang="de">Sie können diesen Benutzer nicht löschen. %s</message>
    <message lang="en">You cannot delete %s. %s</message>
  </error>
  <error type="PERSON-WITH-LOGIN">
    <message lang="fr">Il possède un identifiant d'accès à l'application, vous devez le lui retirer d'abord avec l'interface d'administration</message>
    <message lang="de">Die Person besitzt einen Benutzernamen im System, Sie müssen diesen zuerst in der Rubrik Administration löschen</message>
    <message lang="en">That person has got a login for the application, you have to ask a system administrator to remove that login first.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="PERSON-EMAIL-CONFLICT" code="409">
    <message lang="en">There is already a user %s with the same e-mail address %s, you cannot create two users with the same e-mail address</message>
  </error>
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <!-- *************  Account Errors ************ -->
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <error type="ACCOUNT-MISSING-EMAIL" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Vous devez d'abord renseigner la fiche de la personne avec son adresse de courrier électronique</message>
    <message lang="de">Sie müssen zuerst die Personendaten ausfüllen mit der Adresse und dem E-Mail</message>
    <message lang="en">You have to enter the E-mail address of the person first</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-DUPLICATED-LOGIN" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">L'identifiant "%s" est déjà pris par un autre utilisateur</message>
    <message lang="de">Der Benutzername "%s" wurde bereits von einem anderen Benutzer verwendet</message>
    <message lang="en">The login "%s" already exists for another user</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-MALFORMED-LOGIN" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">L'identifiant du compte doit contenir au minimum 4 caractères alphanumériques y compris le signe - et sans espace</message>
    <message lang="de">Der Benutzername muss mindestens 4 Buchstaben, einschliesslich dem Zeichen - und ohne Leerzeichen beinhalten</message>
    <message lang="en">The login of the account must contain at least 4 caracters and a "-" without any space</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-FORBIDDEN-LOGIN" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Cet identifiant est réservé, merci d'en choisir un autre</message>
    <message lang="en">This login name is reserved, please choose another one</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-CREATE-LOGIN-FAILED" code="500">
    <message lang="fr">La création du nouvel identifiant a échoué, merci de réessayer</message>
    <message lang="de">Die Eingabe des neuen Benutzernamens wurde verweigert, bitte versuchen Sie es erneut</message>
    <message lang="en">The login has not been entered correctly, please try again</message>
  </error>
  <error type="PROTECT-ADMIN-SYSTEM-ROLE" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Vous ne pouvez pas vous retirer à vous même le rôle administrateur, demandez à un autre administrateur</message>
    <message lang="de">Sie können sich nicht selbst die Rolle als Administrator entziehen, fragen Sie einen anderen Administrator</message>
    <message lang="en">You cannot delete your role of administrator, please ask another administrator to do it</message>
  </error>
  <error type="PROTECT-ADMIN-SYSTEM-LOGIN" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Vous ne pouvez pas vous retirer votre propre identifiant, demandez à un autre administrateur</message>
    <message lang="de">Sie können sich nicht Ihren eigenen Benutzernamen entziehen, fragen Sie einen anderen Adiministrator</message>
    <message lang="en">You cannot delete your own login, please ask another administratort to do it</message>
  </error>
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <!-- ***************   Password    ************ -->
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <error type="MISSING-FIELDS" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Soumission incomplète, est-ce que vous avez bien saisi tous les champs demandés ?</message>
    <message lang="de">Eingabe unvollständig, haben Sie alle obligatorischen Felder ausgefüllt ?</message>
    <message lang="en">Incomplete submission, have you really entered all the requested fields?</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-WRONG-EMAIL" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">L'adresse "%s" ne correspond pas à l'adresse enregistrée dans le profil, contactez un administrateur du Case Tracker si vous souhaitez la mettre à jour</message>
    <message lang="en">The address "%s" does not correspond to the one saved in the profile. Please contact an administrator if you need to update your profile</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-NO-EMAIL" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Le profil "%s" est connu de l'application, par contre son adresse de courrier électronique n'est pas renseignée</message>
    <message lang="en">The profile "%s" is known by the application but not the Email address. Please contact an administrator if you need to update your profile</message>
  </error>
  <error type="VALIDATION-NO-PROFILE" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Le profile "%s" n'est pas reconnu par l'application comme ayant un accès autorisé</message>
    <message lang="en">The profile "%s" has no access to the application. Please contact an administrator if you need to update your profile</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SEND-PASSWORD-FAILURE" code="500">
    <message lang="fr">Échec de l'envoi du courrier électronique à "%s", le mot de passe n'a pas été modifié, réessayez ou bien ou contactez un administrateur</message>
    <message lang="en">The sending of the Email addressed to "%s" has failed, the password has not been updated, please try again or contact an administrator</message>
  </error>
  <error type="CHANGE-PASSWORD-FAILURE" code="500">
    <message lang="en">An internal error prevented the modification of your password, your password has not been changed. Please do not take into account the message below and the e-mail that has been sent to "%s" and which contains a new password. Try again later.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-INCONSISTENT-PWD" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Les deux mots de passe proposés sont différents, entrez deux fois le même !</message>
    <message lang="de">Die beiden Passwörter sind nicht identisch, geben Sie zweimal das gleiche Passwort ein</message>
    <message lang="en">The second password is different from the first one, please enter similar passwords!</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-MALFORMED-PWD" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Le mot de passe proposé n'est pas assez complexe : il doit contenir au minimum 8 caractères</message>
    <message lang="de">Das vorgeschlagene Passwort ist nicht komplex genug : es muss mindestens 8 Zeichen beinhalten</message>
    <message lang="en">This password is not complicated enough, it must contain at least 8 characters</message>
  </error>
  <error type="ACCOUNT-PWD-NO-ACCOUNT" code="409">
    <message lang="fr">Cet utilisateur possède un identifiant mais pas d'accès à la base de donnée, pour lui créer un nouveau mot de passe commencez par supprimer son identifiant, vous pourrez ensuite recréer son compte avec le même identifiant, ce qui aura pour effet de lui générer un nouveau mot de passe</message>
    <message lang="en">This user has a login but no valid access to the database. In order to create a new password, please delete the login. Then, recreate the account with the same login. This will generate a new password</message>
  </error>
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <!-- *********** Services Errors ************** -->
  <!-- ****************************************** -->
  <error type="SERVICE-INTERNAL-ERROR" code="500">
    <message lang="en">Error while contacting %s, the service returned : %s</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SERVICE-NOT-RESPONDING" code="404">
    <message lang="en">Impossible to contact %s : the service is not responding. You may try again later or please contact a database administrator.</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SERVICE-ERROR" code="500">
    <message lang="en">Error while contacting %s : %s</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SERVICE-MALFORMED-URL" code="500">
    <message lang="en">Error while contacting %s : malformed URL "%", ask a system administrator to check the configuration</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SERVICE-MISSING" code="500">
    <message lang="en">Impossible to contact %s : the service configuration is incomplete, ask a system administrator to fix it</message>
  </error>
  <error type="SERVICE-FORBIDDEN" code="401">
    <message lang="en">Impossible to call %s : authorization refused</message>
  </error>
</errors>
