<Form Tag="OTF" Layout="fluid"
  xmlns:site="http://oppidoc.com/oppidum/site"
  xmlns:xt="http://ns.inria.org/xtiger"
  xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
  >
  
  <!-- TODO: 
       implement <Component Tag="Term" TypeName="term" src="otf.xml">
       to share component (similar to Include to share complete formulars inside formulars)
   -->
  
  <Component Name="t_term">
    <blockquote xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <p style="font-size:15px;margin-bottom:0.5em">
        I declare that the information included in this application is true and accurate. If my company is selected for the Trade Fair, I agree to observe the terms and conditions laid down in the call for manifestation of interest to the Trade Fair. I also agree to answer to the follow-up questions related to the Trade Fair at the end of exhibition period and upon my return to Europe.
      </p>
      <p style="font-size:15px;margin-bottom:0.5em">
        The information supplied to the SME Instrument - Overseas Trade Fair Participation Programme will be treated in accordance with the European Union (Council Regulation 45/2001) and Chile data protection and privacy laws and regulations. The information will only be used for the internal purposes of the SME Instrument - Overseas Trade Fair Participation Programme. Information will only be made public upon your agreement.
      </p>
    </blockquote>
    <p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
      <label style="display:inline;vertical-align:middle;margin-right:10px;">
        Click here if you agree to the above declaration
      </label>
      <span data-binding="required" data-variable="terms">
        <xt:use param="type=radio;filter=event;value=on" types="input"/>
      </span>
    </p>
  </Component>

  <xt:component name="t_cancellation">
    <p>
      <label style="display:inline;vertical-align:middle;margin-right:10px" id="required">
        Should you be selected to this programme, you will be notified ON. We expect you to follow up on this within 7 days.
      </label>
      <br/>
      <label style="display:inline;vertical-align:middle;margin-right:10px" id="required">
        Cancellations will only be considered in duly documented cases of "force majeure". In any other case, you will be excluded from participating to the SME Instrument - Support to commercialisation services (trade fairs, academy, etc).
      </label>
      <br/>
      <label style="display:inline;vertical-align:middle;margin-right:10px" id="required">
        In case of doubts, please contact our helpdesk.
      </label>
      <br/>
      <label style="display:inline;vertical-align:middle;margin-right:10px" id="required">
        Click here if you agree to the above cancellation policy
      </label>
      <Include src="consent.xml" TypeName="footer"/>
      <xhtml:span data-binding="required" data-variable="terms">
        <xt:use param="type=radio;filter=event;value=on" types="input"/>
      </xhtml:span>
    </p>
  </xt:component>

</Form>
